A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Working Papers of the Vice President, Series 18 FA384
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Press Book (VIII), 1976 July-September 22 (Box 57, Volume 57)
  Remarks, Chartbook Ceremony - Census Bureau, July 1, 1976. Speech, Pageant of Freedom, Washington Monument, July 4, 1976. Toast to Queen Elizabeth, July 8, 1976. Speech, Inaugural Ceremony Albert Einstein Spacearium, July 15, 1976. Press Conference, Wilmington, Delaware, July 19, 1976. Speech, 1976 Victory Kick-off Dinner, Claymont, Delaware, July 19, 1976. Speech, Republican National Hispanic Assembly Reception, Washington, DC, July 29, 1976. Press Conference, Bar Harbor, Maine, August 2, 1976. Press Conference, Seal Harbor, Maine, August 2, 1976. Luncheon Toast to President Kekkonen of Finland, Washington, DC, August 4, 1976. Dinner Toast to President Kekkonen of Finland, Washington, DC, August 5, 1976. Speech, Republican Platform Committee, Kansas City, August 9, 1976. Remarks, Republican National Convention Committee on Resolutions, Kansas City, August 9, 1976. Press Conference, Kansas City, August 12, 1976. Transcript, "Meet the Press," August 15, 1976. Speech, Republican National Convention, August 16, 1976. Speech, Republican National Convention, August 19, 1976. Q&A, White House lawn, September 14, 1976. Speech, Local Republican Reception, Buffalo, NY, September 15, 1976. Remarks, Coffee Rally, Buffalo, NY, September 16, 1976. Press Conference with Senator Dole, Buffalo, NY, September 16, 1976. Remarks, United Airlines Terminal, Rochester, NY, September 16, 1976. Press Conference with Senator Dole, Rochester, NY, September 16, 1976. Remarks, Hancock International Airport, Syracuse, NY, September 16,1976. Press Conference with Senator Dole, Syracuse, NY, September 16, 1976. Remarks, Broome County Airport, Binghamton, NY, September 16, 1976. Press Conference with Senator Dole, Binghamton, NY, September 16, 1976. Press Conference with Senator Dole, NYC, September 16, 1976. Remarks, President Ford Headquarters, New York City, September 16, 1976. Press Conference, Chicago, Illinois, September 21, 1976. Transcript, TV appearance, Chicago, Illinois, September 21, 1976. Speech, Jim Thompson for Governor Dinner, Chicago, Illinois, September 21, 1976. Press Release, re: Campaigning in Cleveland, Columbus, & Cincinnati, Ohio September 22, 1976. Press Conference, Cleveland, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Remarks, Opening of Ford Headquarters, Cleveland, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Speech, Cuyahoga County Republican Breakfast, Cleveland, Ohio, September 22, 1976.
- Press Book (IX), 1976 September 22-October 4 (Box 58, Volume 58)
  Transcript, TV appearance Channel 5, Cleveland, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Speech, Columbus Bar Association Luncheon, Columbus, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Press Conference, Columbus, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Transcript, TV appearance, Columbus, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Press Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Transcript, TV appearance Channel 12, Cincinnati, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Transcript, TV appearance, Cincinnati, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Speech, Hamilton County Republican Rally, Cincinnati, Ohio, September 22, 1976. Remarks, Candidate's Brunch, Hasbrook, New Jersey, September 28, 1976. Press Conference, Dover, New Jersey, September 28, 1976. Speech, Morris County Republican Fund Raiser Luncheon, Dover, New Jersey, September 28, 1976. Press Conference, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, September 28, 1976. Transcript, KYW, "Mike Douglas Show," Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, September 28, 1976. Interview with WCAU TV, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, September 28, 1976. Speech, Salute to Distinguished Republicans Dinner, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, September 28, 1976. Press Conference, Erie, Pennsylvania, September 29, 1976. Transcript, TV appearance WICU-TV, Erie, Pennsylvania, September 29, 1976. Speech, GOP Dinner Support Committee, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, September 29, 1976. Press Conference, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, September 29, 1976. Remarks, Ribbon Cutting Ceremony President Ford Committee, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, September 29, 1976. McPherson Interview, London England, October 4, 1976. BBC Interview, London, England, October 5, 1976. Press Conference, U.S. Embassy, London, England, October 4, 1976. Speech, Opening of North American Indian Art Exhibit, London, England, October 4, 1976.
- Press Book (X), 1976 October 7-19 (Box 59, Volume 59)
  Chronological collection of statements, speeches, press releases and press conference transcripts
  Press Conference, O'Hare Airport, Chicago, Illinois, October 7, 1976. Press Conference, Hilton Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, October 7, 1976. Remarks, Hilton Hotel, Chicago, Illinois, October 7, 1976. Speech, Salute to the President Dinner, Chicago, Illinois, October 7, 1976. Speech, Columbus Citizens Committee Dinner, New York, October 9, 1976. Remarks, New York County Republican Committee Supporter Dinner, New York, October 9, 1976. Speech, Ukrainian-American Congress Committee Annual Dinner, New York, October 9, 1976. Introduction of President, Salute to President Ford Dinner, New York, October 12, 1976. Transcript, KOG-TV appearance on "Jim Dunbar Show," San Francisco, California, October 13, 1976. Press Conference, San Francisco, California, October 13, 1976. Transcript, KCRA-TV appearance, Sacramento, California, October 13, 1976. Press Conference, Portland, Oregon, October 13, 1976. Transcript, KOIN-TV Interview with Ted Bryant, Portland, Oregon, October 13, 1976. Transcript, KGW-TV appearance, Portland, Oregon, October 13, 1976. Remarks, Reception, Portland, Oregon, October 13, 1976. Remarks, VIP Reception, Portland, Oregon, October 13, 1976. Speech, John Spellman Volunteer Breakfast, Seattle, Washington, October 14, 1976. Transcript, Seattle Today Show, Seattle, Washington, October 14, 1976. Press Conference, Seattle, Washington, October 14, 1976. Remarks, Kent County Airport, Grand Rapids, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Speech, Hal Sawyer Luncheon, Grand Rapids, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Speech, Lunch with Rocky, Grand Rapids, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Remarks, Kalamazoo Municipal Airport, Kalamazoo, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Remarks, United Airlines Room, Saginaw, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Speech, Fund Raiser Reception, Saginaw, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Remarks, Ponchartrain Hotel, Detroit, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Transcript, WWJ-TV Channel 4 appearance, Detroit, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Speech, COBO Hall, Detroit, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Speech, Michigan State Republican Committee Dinner, Detroit, Michigan, October 18, 1976. Remarks, Candidate Reception, Bloomington, Minnesota, October 19, 1976. Remarks, Elephant Club, Minneapolis, Minnesota, October 19, 1976. Speech, Elephant Club Luncheon, Minneapolis, Minnesota, October 19, 1976. Remarks, Candidate Rally, Normandale Community College, Bloomington, Minnesota, October 19, 1976.
- Press Book (XI), 1976 October 20-1977 January 18 (Box 60, Volume 60)
  Speech, Joan Braden's Consumer Conference, Washington, DC, October 20, 1976. Q&A, Consumer Conference, Washington, DC, October 20, 1976. Speech, National Press Club, "One Week to Go," Washington, DC, October 26, 1976. Remarks, Senior Citizens Rally, Franklin Square, NY, October 27, 1976. Press Conference, Senior Citizens Rally, Franklin Square, NY, October 27, 1976. Remarks, Women's Tea Rally, Franklin Square, NY, October 27, 1976. Remarks, Reception, Student Complex, Hofstra University, Hempstead, NY, October 27, 1976. Speech, Business, Labor, Education Community Leader Dinner, Hempstead, NY, October 27, 1976. Remarks, Island Park Republican Rally, Island Park, NY, October 27, 1976. Letter to President-Elect Carter, November 3, 1976. Remarks between President and NAR, the Cabinet Room, November 5, 1976. Eulogy for Gus Levy, November 7, 1976. Interview, "US News and World Report," November 9, 1976. Speech, Williamsburg Foundation Dinner, Williamsburg, Vir.ginia, November 12, 1976. Speech, Conference on Future of Productivity, Washington, DC, November 16, 1976. Speech, Republican Eagles Luncheon, Washington, DC, November 16, 1976. Speech, 10 Outstanding Young American Women, Washington, DC, November 16, 1976. Statement, Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services, Washington, DC, November 16, 1976. Remarks, History of Kykuit, Pocantico Hills, November 17, 1976. Speech, 22nd Annual Session of the North Atlantic Treaty, Williamsburg, Virginia, November 18, 1976. Remarks, Ceremony designating John Davison Rockefeller Estate as a National Landmark, Pocantico Hills, November 21, 1976. Speech, 50th Anniversary Celebration of China Institute, NYC, November 30, 1976. Speech, 100th Anniversary of Pakistan's Founder Jinnah, Washington, DC, December 2, 1976. Speech, Georgetown University Graduate Student Forum, Washington, DC, December 8, 1976. Remarks between NAR and Texas Governor John Connally, Washington, DC, December 9, 1976. Speech, Political Science Association, Mount Vernon College, Washington, DC, December 14, 1976. Telegram to Mrs. Daley on the Death of Mayor Daley, December 21, 1976. Remarks, President's Awards for Distinguished Federal Civil Service, Washington, DC, January 12, 1977. Address to the Senate, Washington, DC, January 18, 1977.
- Letters of Appreciation (I) (Box 61, Volume 61)
  Correspondence received by NAR in recognition of his service as Vice President of the United States. Alexandrakis, Menelas - Marsh, John O.
- Letters of Appreciation (II) (Box 62, Volume 62)
  Correspondence received by NAR in recognition of his service as Vice President of the United States. Marshall, Anthony D. - Zehudi, Ruleshi
- Index (Box 63, Volume 63)